A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, John D. Rockefeller, Sr., Series A FA310
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence - Sinclair, I. - Smith, H. (Box 23, Folder 175)
  Sinclair, Iris, December 1927. Sends picture.Sinclair, R., (Mrs.), April 1929. Sends poem.Sinclair Consolidated Oil Company, September 26, 1931. Financial bulletin.Sinclair Pipe Line Company, April 7, 1930. Financial bulletin.Sisson, Minnie, (Mrs. F. N.), April 28, 1928. Sends photos.Sisters of the Good Shepard, April 1920. Sends John D. Rockefeller handiwork, sought to buy land from John D. Rockefeller.Sithmann, Henry, (Mr. and Mrs.), October - November 1920. Personal appeal.Sked, Caroline P., 1926 - 1931. Cleveland friend. Visits. Memories. Condolences.Skidmore, Hazel, November 1927. Interview.Slater, B. J., April - May 1928. John D. Rockefeller sends dime to look alike.Sleepy Hollow Country Club, 1921 - 1924. John D. Rockefeller's membership.Sleeswijk, J. G., June - July 1930. Interview.Sleicher, John A., July 1918. Visit, remembers John D. Rockefeller's remarks.Slovitzky, Michael, January - February 1929. Autographed photograph.Smiley, Daniel and Effie, July 28, 1926. Thanks for gifts.Smith, Barton R., May 5, 1930. Sends picture of Cleveland.Smith, Dorothy, 1919 - 1931. Librarian friend of John D. Rockefeller, gifts.Smith, Edward, May 13, 1924. Thanks for gifts.Smith, Emilie, (Mrs.), September - October 1930. Wedding gift.Smith, Frances M., April 22, 1923. Sends newspaper story.Smith, Frank, November 20, 1931. Sends book.Smith, George P., 1922. Visit.Smith, Gipsy S., Poems.Smith, Harold, (Mr. and Mrs.), December 1923. Wedding gift.
- Correspondence - Smith, H. S. - Solomon (Box 23, Folder 176)
  Smith, Harold S., March 1930. Claims to have warned John D. Rockefeller of assassination attempt, personal appeal.Smith, John M. L., (Mr. and Mrs.), "At home."Smith, Jonathan, (Mrs.), July 1931. Remembers early life at Owego Academy, personal appeal by widow.Smith, Julia T., October 25, 1921. Thanks for gifts to Mrs. Robbins.Smith, Mabel R., (Mrs.), August 1926. Relative, appeal.Smith, Margaret, 1923 - 1924. Gift.Smith, Mary S., October 7, 1927. Thanks for good work.Smith, Milton G., March - April 1924. Sends history of Ormond Beach.Smith, Sherwin H., July - August 1921. Golf.Smith, T. W., 1922 - 1924. Tarrytown minister, visit, church appeal.Smith, Thomas, April 4, 1923. Sends hand made articles.Snape, John, 1925 - 1927; 1931. Minister, Euclid Avenue Baptist Church, visits, gift to church, John D. Rockefeller gift to Carthage, New York Church in 1883.Snipes, Joseph F., November - December 1931. Health plan.Solomon, David, June - July 1921. Birthday congratulations.
- Correspondence - Soper, Alexander C. and Grace, 1920-1929 (Box 24, Folder 177)
  Lakewood. Soper Lumber Company. Golf partner. Marriage of daughter, Elizabeth. Wants to help missionary through Rockefeller Institute. Death of Mr. Soper.
- Correspondence - Southwell - Spelman, J. (Box 24, Folder 178)
  Southwell, George C., July 1931. Euclid Avenue Baptist Church appeal.Spahr, Jean Gurney, August 1924. Wedding gift.Spalding, Zeph S., July - August 1923. Cleveland schoolmate.Spalding, Messrs. A. G. and Brother, April - August 1927. Golf balls.Spasseff, Fraico, August 23, 1926. In French, personal appeal.Speer, Emma B., (Mrs. Robert), January 28, 1929. Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) work.Speer, John Z., 1922 - 1923; 1927. Re: Colorado Fuel & Iron Company, death.Speer, Louis P., (Mrs.), April 1929. Wedding gift.Spelman, Anna R., 1921 - 1932. Thanks for gift.Spelman, Deborah, 1931. Relating Spelman family incident.Spelman, Frank E., 1920 - 1925. John D. Rockefeller gifts.Spelman, Harvey B., June - July 1925. Spelman genealogy.Spelman, Harvey B., January 1927. Seeks interview.Spelman, Herbert F., February 9, 1929. Appeal for college funds.Spelman, Jennie, 1919 - 1923; 1928 - 1931. Gifts, (sister of Lilla).
- Correspondence - Spelman, L. - Spies (Box 24, Folder 179)
  Spelman, Lilla S., 1921 - 1930. Gifts, receives part of Aunt Lute's estate (sister of Jennie Spelman).Spelman, Marion, (Mrs. William C.), June 23, 1921. Appeal.Spelman, Robert W., December 1927. Happy New Year!Spelman Seminary, 1921 - 1931. Progress of work.Spencerian School of Commerce, Accounts and Finance, 1923; 1926 - 1931. Cleveland. John D. Rockefeller attended school 1854. 75th Anniversary celebration. Invitations to attend graduations. Visits with President Merville. Sent etching of 2nd Sargent portrait to hang in administration building. Received Scroll of Distinction.Spicer, (Mrs. R.), July - August 1929. Lace handkerchief.Spies, Charles B., May 22, 1929. From Rockefeller Institute, clipping on Eka Salt.
- Correspondence - Spillane - Spivey (Box 24, Folder 180)
  Spillane, Reverend Maurice R., 1923 - 1931. Catholic church appeal.Spinney, Charles A., January 14, 1927. Sends Indian spear head.Spira, (Mrs. H.), April 28, 1921. Wants to rent her house in Cleveland.Spivey, Ludd M., March 30, 1927. Work of Southern College, Florida
- Correspondence - Splaine, Jennie Davison (Mrs.), 1918-1931 (Box 24, Folder 181)
  Moravia, New York. Continued support.
- Correspondence - Spring - Stephenson (Box 24, Folder 182)
  Spring, James C., July 7, 1931. Seeks interview.Springer, W. J., (Mr.), July 1927. Standard Oil, sends gifts.Springsler, Charles, (Mrs.), January 12, 1922. Thanks for gift.Sprunk, Edward F., August 28, 1930. Thanks for dime.Squire, Andrew, 1924 - 1925. Birthday congratulations.Squite, Fred, (Mrs.), May 27, 1931. Claims relationship.Standard Oil Companies, 1921 - 1922; 1928. Invitations to dinners, increasing dividends.Stangier, Adelaide J., (Mrs.), December 28, 1932. Well wishes.Stanley, John J., October 1926. Sympathy message.Stanton, Elisha W., 1920 - 1923. Cousins, gifts, condolences.Stanton, Nicholas, 1922; 1925. House employee, gifts.Stately, John C., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1920 - 1921. 50th Wedding anniversary greeting.Steely, John D., April 13, 1920. Treatment, living at Pocantico.Stein, Andrew, October 1919. Appeal.Stephan, John F., 1920 - 1931. Dental work, friend.Stephenson, J. E., (Mr.), July 1926. Birthday congratulations.
- Correspondence - Stevens, H. E. - Stringfellow (Box 24, Folder 183)
  Stevens, H. E., February 12, 1931. Appeal.Stevens, J. L., February - April 1929. Asks information.Stewart, John A., August 1923. John D. Rockefeller sends birthday congratulations.Stewart, John A., March 1925. Appeal, George Washington, Sulgrave Institution.Stewart, John N., September 27, 1922. Relating incident re John D. Rockefeller's early working days.Stewart, Lyman, July 22, 1920. John D. Rockefeller sends birthday congratulations.Stewart, R. Franklin, 1920; 1924; 1931. Neighbor Pocantico.Stewart, Colonel Robert W., March 15, 1929. News of Standard Oil former Board Chairman.Stewart, Sarah E., October 1921. Wedding gift.Stewart, W. H., 1921; 1924. Asks information re Standard Oil, appreciation for kindness.Stewart, William B., March 25, 1927. Appreciated Cleveland Chamber of Commerce, has John D. Rockefeller portrait in Chamber hall.Stillman, Ernest G. and family, December 1931. At home.Stilwell, (Mrs.), May 9, 1930. Thanks for milk.Stilwell, J. Howard, July 31, 1920. Wants to buy property.Stoddard, Rev. Frank P., October 1924. Appreciation.Stolzenthaler, Mather, October 1927. Sends gift of magazine subscription, refused.Stone, Patrick T., February 28, 1925. Thanks for dime.Stoneman, Mary V., (Mrs. J. W.), March 1925. Invitation, Palmetto Club luncheon.Stroke, Helen L., May 1930. Appeal.Storms, Estelle V., August 1923. Sends editorial.Story, R. G., September - October 1924. Related incident.Stout, Marguerite A., Thanks for sending save cards.Stovall, Jennie S., (Mrs.), May 27, 1929. Appeal, claims relationship.Strack, Mae W., (Mrs. Henry D.), July 1931. Birthday congratulations.Stratton, Miss Lottie, 1920 - 1931. Thanks for gift.Straus, Nathan, 1922 - 1931. Philanthropist; milk pasteurization work, Rockefeller Institute help; work in Jerusalem, soup kitchens, birthday tribute.Strawberry Festival, Tarrytown, June 26, 1929. Donation.Strayls, C. B., February 24, 1930. Would like to drop by.Street, Anna F., 1920 - 1921. Applies for position of housekeeper.Streeter, W. E., Jr., June 1921. Asks about value of oil certificate.Stringfellow, G. E., April 18, 1930. Wants autographed photo.
- Correspondence - Strong, A. H. - Sutcliffe (Box 24, Folder 184)
  Strong, Dr. Augustus H., 1919 - 1922. Sympathy.Strong, Charles H., May 24, 1920. Sends book "Cleveland's Golden Story."Strong, Eliza L. M., (Mrs.), 1921; 1925. Related through Bessie Rockefeller Strong, family news.Strong, Hattie, (Mrs. Henry), June 1920. Appreciation for Rockefeller Foundation money in the University of Rochester new school of medicine.Strong, John Henry, (Mr. and Mrs.), 1919; 1923 - 1924. Family reunion, wedding presents.Strong, Margaret, 1924; 1933. John D. Rockefeller's granddaughter.Strong, William J. H., February 12, 1929. Wants money to search for Noah's Ark.Stuart, William H., 1925 - 1926. Appeals.Stubbe, C. E., September 18, 1925. Thanks for meeting and seeing Pocantico Hills.Stumm, Frank A. and son Carl, 1920 - 1923; 1930. Thanks for gifts, old Standard Oil employee.Sturtevant, Harold, (Mr. and Mrs.), 1919 - 1932. Thanks for gifts."Success" magazine, September 1925. Sending $5 for joke John D. Rockefeller supposedly sent in and they published using his name, he never sent the joke.Sudman, Lois, February 25, 1930. Wants copy of John D. Rockefeller poem, "I Do It Unto Thee."Sumner, Ralph E., January 1928. Sends indoor golf game.Sunday, Reverend W. A. "Billy", 1920 - 1921. Acquaintance, thanks John D. Rockefeller for idea of using compressed oxygen for his hay fever.Sunderkotter, Florence E., 1930 - 1931. Thanks for gifts.Sutcliffe, Doris K., March 10, 1930. Sends poem she composed in his honor.
- Correspondence - Sutherland - Symington (Box 25, Folder 185)
  Sutherland, Esther Whitney, (Mrs.), August 1926. Old Standard Oil employee.Sutton, Edmund, June 11, 1930. Asks to send message to Calvary Sunday School.Sutton, Julia, August 3, 1921. John D. Rockefeller sends check.Svada, (Mrs.), Lotsi, October 20, 1926. Sympathy.Swaine, (Mrs. George D.), July 6, 1930. Death of Mr. Swaine.Sweeney, John S., 1922 - 1924. Friendly letters, golfing days.Swelye, Nelson, November 5, 1920. Thanks for playing golf at Tarrytown.Swift, L. F., (Mr.), January 5, 1928. Sends Swift & Company annual report.Switzer, Eva, March - April 1924. Thanks for trees; former housekeeper Pocantico Hills.Sylvia, Palmedia, February 1929. Thanks for Rockefeller Institute's help in curing her spinal meningitis.Symington, Edith, (Mrs. Albert), March - April 1928. Appeal Horace Taft School.
- Correspondence - Tabernacle Baptist Church - Tarrytown First Baptist Church (Box 25, Folder 186)
  Tabernacle Baptist Church, November - December 1929. Appeal.Tanner, H. C., April 21, 1927. Wants dime.Tapley, Lucy Hale, (Miss), 1919 - 1920; 1930. Work of President Spelman Seminary.Taplin, C. G., (Mrs.), September 1922. Sympathy.Taplin, Frank E., 1922 - 1926. Golf Partner.Tappen, Mary J., 1927. Death.Tappy, Thomas N., December 17, 1931. Elks, Christmas appeal for needy children.Tarbell, Gelrge S., September - November 1920. Police protection in Ithaca, New York.Tarrytown Civic League, 1926 - 1927. Contributions.Tarrytown Community Chest, 1928 - 1922. Contributions.Tarrytown First Baptist Church, 1921 - 1931. John D. Rockefeller contributions.
- Correspondence - Tarrytown Hospital Association - Thornton (Box 25, Folder 187)
  Tarrytown Hospital Association, 1921 - 1923. Contributions, fresh eggs.Tarrytown "Press Record", November 24, 1920. Discontinues subscription.Tarrytown Salvation Army, March 1920. Contribution.Tate, John C., November 29, 1929. Sends design of souvenir medal for consideration.Taylor, Reverend Frederick E., January - February 1930. Appreciation for gift to ministers and missionaries benefit board.Taylor, J., August 31, 1925. Thanks for dime.Taylor, Jeanette R., 1921; 1926. Birthday congratulations.Taylor, William Son & Company, March 18, 1927. Wants John D. Rockefeller congratulatory message for its 57th anniversary, (John D. Rockefeller early office located above store in old Cushing Block).Tayman, Colonial Charles E., 1927 - 1929. Golf partner, sends imperial prunes.Teagle, Walter C., 1920 - 1929. Works for John D. Rockefeller, Jr., sends gifts, book "Evolution of Oil Industry", salmon.Tennant, John H., December 1927. Sends magazine of John D. Rockefeller golfing.Terkiule, Cora B., February 19, 1927. Thanks for cake.Terry, General Marshall O., 1926; 1929. Mutual friend.Thirkettle, Rebecca, February 1, 1927. Birthday congratulations.Thomas, (Mrs.), June 9, 1921. Birthday greetings and request to change German marks, (broken English).Thomas, Andrew J., December 1925. Architect, visit with John D. Rockefeller.Thomas, (Mrs. Jane), June 9, 1929. Appeal.Thomas, Calvin P., (Dr.), 1925 - 1926; 1930. Financial difficulties, death.Thomas, Evan J., March 30, 1931. Appeal.Thomas, Flora W., December 1928. Standard Oil and the "Joint" (patent coupling) claim, 1870's patent violation.Thomas, W. W., December 3, 1921. Comments on "Random Reminiscences."Thomas, Reverend William J. D., 1929. Thanks for dime, sends pennies.Thompson, Arthur R., February 1930. Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) appeal.Thompson, D. F., (Dr.), 1926 - 1929. Baptist church appeal.Thompson, Edward L., (Dr.), 1927 - 1928. Dental work, Daytona.Thompson, J. B., 1921 - 1923. Recommendation, death.Thompson, James K., October 25, 1930. Golf partner.Thompson, M. H., (Mrs.), September 7, 1931. Condolence.Thompson, Mary C., October 1927. Wedding gift.Thompson, Norma S., March 25, 1925. Thanks for help in Ormond.Thompson, Robert M., March 28, 1927. Sends magazine.Thompson, Willard C., July 21, 1921. Acknowledge receipt of cockerel.Thoms, C. M., February 1, 1927. Regards.Thomson, James K., 1927 - 1930. John D. Rockefeller golf instructor, sends golf clubs, balls.Thomson, Jimmie, (Mr. and Mrs.), Thanksgiving greetings.Thornton, Maux, (Mrs. Macon), 1928. Sympathy.
- Correspondence - Thorp - Trigg (Box 25, Folder 188)
  Throp, P. H., (Mr.), May 1929. "Scott's" Journal, seeks information.Thorson, Mary, June 12, 1925. Wedding congratulations.Thresher, Eleanor, March 22, 1930. Thanks for dimes and poem.Thron, J. E., (Mr.), January 12, 1922. Claims to be Standard Oil employee, aid for son.Thwing, Charles J., (Dr.), 1921 - 1922. President Western Reserve University, sends article on Harper, greetings.Tibbetts, Armand R., November 1921. Wants to take landscape architecture class through Pocantico Hills gardens.Tiffany & Company, 1922 - 1923. Storage, bills, fixing articles.Tilghman, Sidel, (Mr. and Mrs.), 1925 - 1927. Ormond neighbor, death.Tillett, Wilburn F., January 17, 1931. Thanks for New Year's greetings.Tillotson, Edwin G., 1930. Birthday and Christmas greetings.Timpson, Caroline M., May - June 1929. Sets "I Do It Unto Thee" to music and asks it to be published.Tims, J., April 14, 1926. Appeal.Tioga County General Hospital, March 22, 1929. Appeal.Titus, Addie G., (Mrs. F. E.), February 1929. Seeks interview.Todd, (Mrs. Ralph T.), November 7, 1927. American Red Cross appeal.Tomlin, W. P., (Mr.), 1922; 1927; 1930. Employee, helps while ill.Tomlinson, E. T., (Dr.), 1925; 1931. Interview, death.Tomplins, Charles P., July 1929. Sends cane birthday gift, returned.Toeery, George B., August 5, 1929. Seeks interview.Touzeau, Anna J., (Mrs.), 1925; 1928 - 1931. Cleveland acquaintance, thanks for gifts.Towl, Forrest M., August - September 1923. Sympathy.Townsend, James B., 1922 - 1923. Nut.Tracy, Corinth, 1926 - 1927. Wedding present, visit.Trader, Georgia D., February 24, 1930. John D. Rockefeller poem in Braille, "I Do It Unto Thee."Training School for Public Service, March 1920. Contribution.Travis, Mary W., (Mrs. Thomas), March 1930. Asks information.Treadwill, Harriet B., 1920 - 1931. Continued gifts.Treadwell, Thomas P., Jr., August 10, 1922. Thanks for dimes, DeLap's nephew.Treat, Florence Gray, (Mrs.), November - December 1920. Thanks for helping her.Trigg, Ernest T., February 1923. Temple University appeal.
- Correspondence - Tripp - Tuttle, M. (Box 25, Folder 189)
  Tripp, A. J., (Mrs.), 1920 - 1930. Continued gifts.Troxell, Johnson M., 1923 - 1929. Friendly letters.Troy, John P., 1921 - 1922; 1928. Photographer-Cornell, reprint photos for John D. Rockefeller.Trueblood, Wilbur T., Jr., 1930. Ivy Lee's nephew, wants photo.Truett, Reverend George W., (Dr.), 1927; 1930. Appreciation of work, sends book.Trull, Fannie E., 1921 - 1923. Thanks for visits at Lakewood.Tucker, William H., July 11, 1929. Golf course and turf engineers, wants work.Tupper, Fred W., 1929 - 1931. Photographer, work for John D. Rockefeller.Turgeon, Frank, Jr., February 10, 1927. Portrait photographer, work for John D. Rockefeller.Turnbull, George, July 1923. "The Derick" newspaper, sends editorial.Turner, Cora L., May 14, 1924. Seeks interview.Turner, William J., (Mrs.), 1920 - 1923. Sympathies.Tusculus College, March 11, 1931. John D. Rockefeller sends message.Tuttle, Edna Preston, (Mrs.), 1927 - 1928. Job applicant, many references.Tuttle, (Mrs. Martha M.), 1921 - 1922; 1926. Once John D. Rockefeller's secretary, gifts, death.
- Correspondence (U) (Box 25, Folder 190)
  Underwood, Nina W., June 3, 1924. Wedding gift.Underwood & Underwood, October 1927. Wants to take portrait photos.Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1919 - 1926. Contributions.United States Department of Agriculture, January 1930. Re: restriction on plant bulbs sent unsolicited from Germany to John D. Rockefeller.United States Rubber Company 1927 - 1928. Sends golf balls.United States Survey Company, June 1922. Sends New England road guide.University of Chicago Club of Florida, February 16, 1929. News.Updegraff, Gertrude, (Mrs. Harlan), February - March 1926. Cornell College, appeal, Iowa.Upshaw, William D., 1927 - 1928. Book, anniversary invitation.Upshur, George L., December 26, 1929. Book supporting Standard Oil Company.U'Ren, W. S., (Mr.), July 1927. Appreciation of work.Urquhart, (Mrs. William), 1922 - 1931. Thanks for gifts, husbands job.Uruma, T. H., December 1930. Sends photos as appreciation.
- Correspondence - Vacuum Oil Company - Van Duyne (Box 25, Folder 191)
  Vacuum Oil Company, May 6, 1931. Report.Vaille, Frederick O., 1926 - 1927. Thanks for dime, sends his "pascal" celery.Valdivia, Rafael, March - April 1929. Wants dime.Valentin, Nicola, August 8, 1928. Sends John D. Rockefeller photo.Van Arsdale, (Mrs. Dorr), 1920; 1926 - 1927; 1930. Sympathy.Van Arsdale, Ama, January 14, 1931. Thanks for photo.Vance, Lucie F., 1918 - 1930. Friendly letters and gifts.Vanderbilt, Charles, February 20, 1928. Sends poem.Vanderbilt, Cornelius, Jr., 1931. Seeks interview for paper.Vanderbilt, William, (Mr. and Mrs.), 1925 - 1926. Wedding announcements.Vanderblue, Homer B., July - August 1922. Northwestern University, wants autographed photo.Vandergrift, J. W., (Mr.), June 2, 1924. Introduction.Vanderlip, Frank A., 1927. New York County educational work appeal, wedding invitation.Vanderveer, A., (Dr.), 1920 - 1928. Friendly letters, appreciation of work.Van Duesen, G. C., (Mr.), August 1922. Standard Oil employee.Van Duyne, (Mr. J. Burr and family), 1921 - 1931. Auburn, New York cousins, gifts, visits.
- Correspondence - Van Dyke - Vincent (Box 25, Folder 192)
  Van Dyke, J. W., (Mr.), 1926 - 1931. President, Atlantic Refining Company, then Chairman of the Board. Golfing partners. Visits. Oil business.Vannatter, Elsie, (Mrs.), October - November 1928. Sends picture of John D. RockefellerVanness, I. J., (Mr.), December 30, 1929. Appreciation of gift to Southern Baptist Convention.VanNorden, (Mrs.), January 18, 1920. Wants autograph.Van Rees, Cornelius, 1922 - 1923. Thanks for visits.Van Sweringen, O. P., 1920 - 1921. Business, friendly matters.Van Tassel, Nettie S., 1921. Thanks for letter.Van Tassell, Martha N., April 20, 1926. Thanks for sympathy.Van Wagner, Margaret, July 8, 1927. Birthday congratulations.Varrelman, F. A., September 10, 1928. Wants part of John D. Rockefeller estate for extension of Bronx Botanical Gardens.Vassar College, 1918 - 1919; 1927; 1931. John D. Rockefeller gifts.Vaughan, Harold S., May 28, 1925. Thanks for interview.Vedder, (Mrs.), January 12, 1930. Thanks for help.Ventard, A., (Mr.), July - August 1927. Birthday congratulations.Verbinnen, Henri E., August 1921. Business proposition.Veresh, D. Joe, 1930. Business proposition.Verity, Martha, January 1928. Sends pen and ink sketch of John D. Rockefeller.Vermont, University of, August 1929. Appeal.Verrill, Ethel B., (Mrs.), August 1921. Appeal.Veterans of Foreign Wars, February - April 1931. Pleased he is denouncing communism. Gift of Patriotic framing documents.Vilas, Malcom G., September 1922. Sends photo of circular of Clark, Gardner & Company, March 1, 1860.Vincent, George, (Dr.), 1924 - 1926; 1930. Works for Rockefeller Foundation, friendly letter, visits.
- Correspondence - Virginia-Carolina Chemical Company - Vystavelova (Box 26, Folder 193)
  Virginia-Carolina Chemical Company, June 25, 1919. John D. Rockefeller leave increase of dividends for further consideration.Vita Glass, January 1928. John D. Rockefeller interest, filtering sun's ultra violet rays.Volusia County, Florida Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), February 1922. Contribution.Volz, Dora and Will, 1923; 1927 - 1930. Gifts.Vystavelova, Zdenka, September 2, 1929. Appeal.
- Correspondence - Wade, D. B. - Walker, Ralph (Box 26, Folder 194)
  Wade, Dorothy B., January - May 1927. Wants Walter James Barren to give organ recital for John D. Rockefeller.Wade, Jeptha H., March 1926. Condolence.Waernier, Elizabeth, June - October 1928. Sends album of engravings and stamps.Wagner, Charles, April - May 1921. Chauffeur, John D. Rockefeller recommendation.Wagar, Marie, 1924. Thanks for dime.Wakefield, Anna M., 1923; 1926. Thanks for visit.Walburn, Albert W., 1924 - 1928. Seeks interview.Walfron, Frederick A., July 1930. Birthday congratulations sent to golf club.Walker, Reverend Charles T., 1919 - 1926. Baptist church, thanks for contributions.Walker, Elenora, (Mrs.), 1923 - 1926; 1930. Ghanks for gifts.Walker, Glencora, 1931. Thanks for picture.Walker, Reverend Harry G., 1928 - 1931. Appeals.Walker, Reverend Ralph, 1930 - 1931. Pastor, Euclid Avenue Baptist Church. Appreciation of gifts, contributions, John D. Rockefeller sends poem, "I Do It Unto Thee."
- Correspondence - Walker, Ray B. - Warner, Edward (Box 26, Folder 195)
  Walker, Ray B., 1922 - 1931. Union Free School principal, Pocantico Hills, gifts.Walker, U. S., (Mr.), February 1927. Sends book.Walker, William B., 1921. Appreciates work.Walkowitz, A., (Mr.), July 29, 1929. Sends sketches.Wallace, Andrew B., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1920 - 1924. Daughter's weeding; death.Wallace, Dora O., (Mrs.), September 1920. Invites him up to Owego, New York. Waller, Glenora, (Mrs.), 1919 - 1922; 1926; 1930. Cleveland friend, appeal.Wallis, Robert, (Dr.), March - April 1926. Appreciates work.Walton, John W., April 1922. Appeal.Walton, Margaret, August 3, 1928. Thanks for dimes.Wanamaker, John, 1920; 1922. Appreciates fork.Warburg, Felix M., July 17, 1921. Thanks for contribution to Nurses' Service.Ward, Frances, July 1926. Appeal.Ward, Henry C., September 30, 1930. Challenge to game of golf.Waring, Orville T., 1921 - 1923. Standard Oil executive, John D. Rockefeller friend, death.Warmack, Robert N., (Mrs.), August 1927. Marriage announcement.Warner, Edward R., (Mr.), Old school mate at Owego Academy, friendly letters.
- Correspondence - Warner, Eva F., 1919-1921 (Box 26, Folder 196)
  Mrs. Ira Warner and family. Good friend, visits.
- Correspondence - Warner, Eva F., 1922-1924 (Box 26, Folder 197)
- Correspondence - Warner, Eva F., 1925-1927 (Box 26, Folder 198)